[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":66889,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":146536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":18198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":164737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":166988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":6366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":173355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3663,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":177019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":183862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1353,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":185217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"-4","response_history":["-4"],"rt":61978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":247197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":4933,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":252134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's you r result . If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6049,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":258184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1302,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":259487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":262777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":945,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":263723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":276490,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1234,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":277726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7451,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":285178,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1051,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":286230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4541,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":290772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":292205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5469,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":297675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1133,"trial_type":"feed back","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":298809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":20834,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":319646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity un der +<su b>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":52295,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":371942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":21587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":393533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1623,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":395160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (R emember,  the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4957,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":400119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1013,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":401135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":403912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1130,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":405044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":408031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":408992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 und er +<sub >6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":412072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":15739,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":427815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":34431,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":462249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":84314,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":546566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generato r is an  element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":57790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":604361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":5748,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":610114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":614576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry , that's  incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":27026,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":641603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":29772,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":671378,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator und er +<sub >6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":10672,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":682053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":27925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":709980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1590,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":711571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions a bout a n ew operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":96474,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":808047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":815528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1238,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":816768,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":821259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":828102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4954,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":833058,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3026,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":836088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":841298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":848639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 I added 8 and 4 and then subtracted 9. ","response_history":["3 I added 8 and 4 and then subtr acted 9.  "],"rt":32733,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":881376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 It is zero because it gives you the identical number when it's combined with another number.","response_history":["0 It is zero because it gives you th eidentical number","0 It is zero because it gives you theidentical number","0 It is zero because it gives you the identical number when it's combined with another number."],"rt":79386,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":960764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":43685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1004452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1008312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9. ( minus 9 gives us 0.","response_history":["6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 u","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is adeed","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is adee","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is ade","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9 and ","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9 and","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9 an","6 It is  6 becaus e when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9 a","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9 ","6 It is 6 because when 6 and 3 is added, we get 9. ( minus 9 gives us 0."],"rt":37764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1046078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because we can't make the odd numbers using 2","response_history":["No because we can't make the odd numbers using 2"],"rt":2364189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":3410272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using just 3","response_history":["Yes,  because  it can be used ","No, because we can't make 4 or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4,  or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5 or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5,  or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7  or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 5 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or  using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using 3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using j3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using ju3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using jus3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using just3","No, because we can't make 4, 5, 7 or 8 using just 3"],"rt":89027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":3499302,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, because we can make all the numbers using 5","response_history":["Yes, because we can make all the numbers using 5"],"rt":55841,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":3555145,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because we cant make all of the numbers using 6","response_history":["No, because w e c","No, because w e ","No, because w e","No, because w ","No, because we cann't ","No, because we cann't","No, because we cann'","No, because we cann","No, because we cant make all of the numbers using 6"],"rt":198439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":3753586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive count ing numb er. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":17344,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":3770934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+n1","response_history":["1","=1","1","=1","=n1","n1","+n1"],"rt":144832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":3915771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n1 This is how the formula is written. 1 is going to be comb ined wit h x.","response_history":["x+n1 This is how the formula is written. 1 is going to be combined with x."],"rt":67920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":3983695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Odd numbers are not generators.","response_history":["Odd numbers are not ger","Odd numbers are not generators."],"rt":72956,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":4056652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":18704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":4075361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":5279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":4080644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":4086782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret. ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Because if its not a generator, it must be an odd number. It has to be a multiple of divisor in order for it be right.","response_history":["Because ","Because if its not a generator, it must be an odd number ","Because if its not a generator, it must be an odd number. It has to be a multiple of divisor in order for it be right."],"rt":234571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":4321355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":4331109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an  element  x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Because it can't be always a generator under +n.","response_history":["Because it can't be always a generator under +n."],"rt":24001,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":4355111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":4366683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask  you some  questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2566,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":4369251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":4372115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3488,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":4375604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"W hat is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Math 132. I do not remember the title of the class. It was some kind of statistics I think.","response_history":["Math 132. I do not remember the titleof t","Math 132. I do not remember the titleof ","Math 132. I do not remember the titleof","Math 132. I do not remember the titleo","Math 132. I do not remember the title of the class. It was some kind of statistics I think."],"rt":45049,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":4420655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or r ecently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":9086,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":4429745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":4435692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not  at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":4982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":4440676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":4445052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":4449329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":4451358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Pashto","response_history":["Pashto"],"rt":5567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":4456926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":4648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":4461575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do yo u have a ny comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The last concept was really hard for me to get. I tried my best but I don't think I got it right. The rest of the concepts were easy and I really enjoyed learning them. Thank you.","response_history":["The last concet ","The last concet","The last concept was really hard for me to get. I tried my best but I don't think I got it right. The rest of the concepts were easy and I really enjoyed learning them. Thank you."],"rt":41137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":4502714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]